let's go
hey ain't nobody like me
it's bad day oh
ain't nobody like me 어머니 땜에 맛있을 수
있어 그래서 그 어머니 방에
넣어 놓으려고 이따가 다음 손님 말씀하시면요 응 근데 어머니 방에 넣어
놓으려고 응 아직 한시 한시 때 올 줄 거야
지금 몇 시예요 지금 한 시예요 딱 한 시입니다
음 음 음 근데
어떻게 딱 퍼스널 컬러에 맞춰서 다 갖고 오셨네요 아 그래 어제도 이
커튼 막 잘 맞았어 아 그래 에 블랙도 잘 어울리고 화이트도 잘 어울리고
있던 거였어 있던 거 이 색깔도 잘 어울리고
hmm what time welcome hi welcome hi welcome
hi welcome to dangle how are you oh my gosh
nice to meet you I'm Mira hi nice to meet you oh my God hello
hello so beautiful how are you
what's your name Lisa Lisa yes oh my gosh you're all so beautiful
we are so excited thank you hi nice to meet you oh my gosh hello OK
this is consultation room okay
that's why you're so beautiful
oh my gosh I'm so beautiful because of her and she ha
ha I can see it oh thank you thank you
you guys are like twins you know I'm very lucky to have her face
same same color of your hair you know
very similar we have the same style so yeah
okay you're a very hot influencer oh you are a tiktoker yeah
I got nothing left to ah I went to Seoul to in Korea yes
and I was able to have my makeup done professionally there
um how was it
it was wonderful oh my gosh
it was wonderful I got to I
I have never had a makeover
so I'm very excited this is your first time to make yes yes
and I'm so happy to be able to share this experience together
yeah we're really excited
yes
so I'm so excited wonderful yes
do you guys have any like a certain look or picture or reference
I believe I might be due for some styling of the bangs
um just please not too short hahaha
I have always had a hard time determining what
styles are the most complimentary
yes they're gonna doing their magic to
you know wonderful
oh so I'm excited
so excited to show her off
my name is Jenna Renee I'm 24 years old
my mom is my best friend uh
we're attached at the hip
and my mom and I were dying for a makeover
my mom hasn't had the pleasure of being as spoiled as me
and I really wanted to bring her out and show her off
익스텐션 해야 되겠는데
봐봐요 잘 어울려
봐 줄게 어 저 양쪽에 한번 해주시면 안 돼요 자 여기 아이 키가 안
닿아가지고 둘 둘 둘분 해줘요 따똥
아 그렇구나 ㅎㅎ
그렇구나 뭐예요 아 와 할 말이 없어 ㅎㅎ 뭐라고요 참 참 저
오늘부터 메이크업 어시스턴트로 갈게요 아니 아니야 미안해
저를 아 그렇구나
저도 진짜 솔직하게 할게요 이제 아니 왜 그러는데
나한테도 네 저도 솔직하게 해요 아 우리 우리
얼마 안 남았는데 어 마지막 날인데 어 사이좋게 한국으로
돌아가야지 크나큰 크나큰 상처를 주시고
아 그렇구나 하 하 하 하 그렇구나
please follow me
can I say hey
what does that taste like it's kind of uh sweet
I drink all mine that was really good
how's the drink all right are you good delicious thank you so much
I made it yeah it was great hahaha
can you guys wait for a bit please yeah it's gonna take like 5 minutes
okay yeah no worries thank you
I'm so excited about those
do you remember when I used to beg you for hair extensions
so beautiful oh thank you yeah
looks so good oh thank you same in law
yeah yes oh thank you oh my God just a minute yeah oh no worries
everyone's so sweet I know
hi I'm makeup artist for Gina
nice to meet you nice to meet you Gina oh
you look so pretty you look so pretty thank you I know her at least
and you do yes
hi yeah so so super famous right oh no yeah
you're so beautiful too oh my God thank you isn't she
yeah she's so beautiful amazing
the mask back let's do the mask back first
yeah it's your turn so who ha ha
your face is so small thank you 여기가 입인데 여기 지금 밑에 내려간
거지 그런 거구나 어허 어쩐지 어쩐지 얼굴이 너무 작으셔가지고
OK then thank you
but I guess my face is small
hahaha
are you guys ready
what's wrong
she's gonna run away like hmm
yeah okay now I'm done
wow
oh
yeah
hahaha
we have to go
oh my God
I love it
are you so excited
you can't help it huh I can't help myself
should we go for a makeup
yeah yeah
hello
what do you like to get this
here is I um
I love a soft glam look I love ah
do you like soft glam look
wow okay
I trimmed your bangs and cut them back
oh thank you
to shape oh
I'm so excited so exciting
yeah yeah
I'm so excited I saw the year and inside clip you do so amazing
thank you that time wow
Disney princess oh
who are you so beautiful
thank you so much it's many Korean people
oh so amazing
it's a beautiful face oh
you're on the video right
yeah in the coffee
I was just a barista wow
I used to do barista too barista yeah
yeah I knew it
you knew it
I made it
it takes one to know one yeah
it's always very
I think um
that job taught me how to talk to
oh really talk to um
customers like so sociable
yeah yeah
sociable
cut the part of my hair for me
like trim the your bangs definitely need a little shaping
내가 분위기 있어 보이지 와 이쁘다 와우 이츠 베리 나이스
I'm going to keep you everywhere I go
yeah hahaha
make a room should we move to make a room
sounds great sounds great
okay let's go
hello welcome
yeah hello
so come here please
hi hi
I feel like a princess yes
princess
I'm so excited yeah
in the future best face mask
Jenna you need to analyze your skin condition now
so I'm going to use this machine to how your skin condition is now
very new and very smart machine
wow
now does this tell you if there's any sun damage or anything
yes oh OK
oh no
don't worry about it it's very common OK
so
I'm going to scan your skin just forehead area first
okay so haha
oh oh
haha
cause you are only Chinese right
yes so it's um
and wrinkles wrinkles
oh no
it's starting it's starting
you just hit the bottom at the hydration
oh my
yes we gotta fix that
yeah I'll do that for sure
drink a lot of water I will
oh yeah
that's nice and cooling
yeah you can use it as facial mask pack as well
that's a perfect idea to protect from the heat
how do you feel that feels so nice on the skin
nice and cool oh
okay let's eyelash color first
look down please
thank you bye
have you ever done your makeup by a professional before
I have um
I've had my makeup done professionally in Seoul actually Seoul yes
that was absolutely wonderful
um I remember how they curled my lashes with the lighter and the stick
and I was like was that right
a K beauty thing or is that just
do you know this skill no
I have no idea what you're doing
I'm like it makes your lashes more curly
oh
no like this
I wasn't sure it is K beauty thing
yes so I am just absolutely spoiled
um
with having my makeup done
it was the best experience of my life
I enjoyed that so much
that I would love to be able to take my family back and spoil them
like that was a great experience all within its own
and your mom is so beautiful
I really think so too
that's why I was excited to bring her along
because she doesn't recognize how beautiful yeah she can be and is
she is so beautiful yeah
can you touch your face it feels really cool
not your face hits gone right
that's like I put my face in the refrigerator it's so nice
it's ready to wake up right now
쫓겨나요 그럼
그럼 쫓겨나면 안 되지
세
개짜리 있어
if you put them in the basement
요거 하나만 꾸며드려도 좋아요
방에 네 명이 계세요 네 음
그 시안 한 번만 더 볼 수 있을까요 시안 네 알았어요
아 진짜 예쁘게 해 주고 싶은데 이분 아
너무 피부도 너무 좋고 이게
이목구비가 너무 예쁘셔서 아 이분은
좀 뭔가 진짜 블링블링한 그냥 좀 화사한 느낌 연출해 드리고 싶었습니다
그리고 또 오늘 완전 핫핑크 아우트피스를 가지고
오셨기 때문에 거기에 어울리는 약간 바비 인형같이 좀
그런 룩으로 소프트한 핑크에 스파클링한 포인트들 좀 그런 부분들을 좀
강조 그런 부분들을 좀 강조했어요
and it's the skincare makeup
looks nice brightening not too much
I usually buy
2 uh at least two color uh huh uh one color is natural color
and the out other outside uh huh and the bright color the middle side
more looks dimension oh
yeah brings more of a very own yeah
this matte foundation is really good on you
okay eyeliner first
look at the mirror please
look at this oh I love this shape okay do you know
uh what do what do you think this liner looks
really like a Korean and or looks like cat's eye
like this one which one do you like this one or this one
which do you think
would look better with my eye I'm thinking maybe more of a cat eye
uh huh a little bit more cat eye let's go yeah sure
do you know this tool
it's a cotton swab
oh yeah cotton swab like a
you can make eyeliner like after that and you erase it just like that
yeah I'm so excited I use Q Tips and then I just erase it all and then
wipe it off and yeah oh my gosh
easy yeah easy peasy this is a dream I'm so excited to buy
those for eyeliner
근데 이건 진짜 백이면 백 다 신기하세요 메이크업에 너무 관심이 많으시고
케이비티 제품들 이미 많이 사용하시는 분이라 이런 메이크업 팁들이나
메이크업 도구들에 관심 진짜 많으시더라고요
close eyes
OK great great
yes oh my God
oh my God
haha alright
this so natural wow yeah right no
딱 이거 올리면 또 이거대로 예뻐지고 그렇게 너무 재밌는 거예요 에
메이크업을 너무 확
확 받는 얼굴이잖아요 그니까 메이크업을 너무
다양하게 소화할 수 있는 얼굴이어서 처음 동다라 기분 좋아졌던 거 같아요
it's really fun to make you up thank you so much
makeup I look so pretty yes ah so pretty
I think we need this one
your reaction so nice
so good
this glitters on it yeah
let's do the sparkle sparkle one more
hmm wow auntie duh I'm breaking out right now
oh
it's adding an extra sparkle to your eye I love that I love it
so pretty I feel like a pop star yeah
I can't wait anymore every time I look at you
with this tweezer like this like this one by one
that makes a world of difference oh my gosh that's gorgeous
I'm breaking I'm going home and buying glitter because this is
so exciting
I'm going to be taking all of your tips and tricks
yes you should come with me right in my pocket yeah hahaha
you're a genius so funny Jenna
I love your energy I'm breaking out hi Jenna
hello oh my God how is it going
did you make a princess or a man to rescue you tonight
지금 천천히 한번 하고 있습니다 천천히 하고 있어요 아
she's so pretty she is so freaking gorgeous
너무 이쁘다 재밌지 아 너무 예뻐서 너무 재밌어요 나도 놀라겠다
엄마가 약간 케이스타일 메이크업 받은 거 처음 볼 거 아니야 그니까 응
wow
yeah like a diamond yeah
hi okay let's get some makeup time okay yeah
wow wow you have such a great skin texture oh thank you cool okay
so uh what makeup do you want for today
day to day basis I don't really wear much makeup
uh huh I'm a teacher so a cross between glam and oh really casual
a little bit glam a little bit yes yeah uh huh uh huh
I usually wear very light makeup
I'm in the classroom all day long with little kids so
I don't get an opportunity to really do my makeup up for big events
uh how about your daughter's character
I wonder um her personality she has a good sense of humor oh
quite funny and silly at times hahaha so cute hahaha
the same with you oh pretty much yes wow yeah
she takes after me quite a bit on many current characteristics oh
she is definitely my mini me
I can't deny her that's for sure she looks too much like me so
we have a very tight relationship
we spend a lot of time together
like I said she's just a great girl to be around and I I love
spending time with her
and then
I think you have a such a little bit blue dark circle
uh huh some vein on your a lid
it looks little bit a redness okay
so I'm gonna use the opposite color for this
oh yeah okay
green one so the first for the under eye
and then some mint color mix it on near the water line okay
okay open your eyes
it looks great yeah it's good
so I'm gonna uh
do a makeup for you like a uh
the Koreans everyday makeup look perfect
yeah it's good okay
I know that's right
and then we also we can use the brush with the eyeliner colour okay
yeah like it yeah deep expressive
do you love to watch this area
yeah it looks like a connect the wing right
yes
I think it's good on you uh
with the eyeliner uh
with the eyeshadow color oh OK
yeah not eyeliner
so that's why almost Korean love this
I will take you home so you can do my makeup every day
every day yeah
I hope so
that sounds great
리사 옵니다 리사 어머님 먼저 나오신대 어머님이 모델
같으신데 키가 크셔가지고 그리고 진짜 똑같이 생겼어
wonderful
oh so excited so excited to show her off
I'm not one that wears a lot of makeup
usually so I was excited about the makeup
hey come on Lisa
beautiful
oh
haha
oh my God
oh beautiful oh my God so looks so young
oh my God so useful
yeah I love it
you guys did wonderful so pretty
oh thank you
thank you yeah
you can just tell everyone you're the door
yeah hahaha
yeah oh my gosh
your hair is amazing oh
my God it is yeah yeah
oh my
oh my gosh so fun
she look great we married that
I guess so
this is a fun experience yeah yeah
oh my gosh
so fun
Jenna get out of here
so we are waiting for Jenna
yeah OK
so excited to see her almost getting done
yeah yeah
just waiting on her excited
just put concealer thin thin line on it hmm
you did just the perfect wave
yes it's perfect wave hmm
너무 이쁘다 메이크업 너무 이뻐요 와 이쁘다
it's not a human hahaha angel angel
you touched my heart wow so amazing so good at what you do
진짜 헐리우드 스타네 너무 이 너무
닮았어요 똑같이 너무 닮았다 와우
you look so Good
하하 땡큐 제나 옵니다
제나 옵니다
um I went to Seoul to in Korea I am just absolutely spoiled um
with having my makeup done
yeah I enjoyed that spa
I would love to be able to take my family back and spoil them like
so we're very excited to see what you're able to do with her
oh oh my God
oh my God wow beautiful
just 24 hours in a place that we can ah oh my god
oh
wow beautiful
oh wow she's so beautiful you look so beautiful
I love this hair on you so much
oh my gosh look at it
turn around turn around
you look gorgeous I'm so excited to take her out and show her off
you guys did a what a wonderful job
how good are your jobs are you
oh my gosh thank you guys so much
you guys are amazing thank you
yeah do you want to do a spin
oh
she's got it down hahaha
yeah it is
I love to use makeup to accentuate my features
and to make my eyes pop and bigger
or looks like cat's eye like this one
where's my look of motion
think this lashes looks really good on you
this so natural yeah
that looks good again oh that just did it
gorgeous pads
I would say my one insecurity is my nose
my biggest insecurity
just put concealer thin thin line on it
to draw your nose with X
you go to more narrow like this point
the X is very helpful
sparkle sparkle
like a diamond
I couldn't be more obsessed with this makeover
I wish we could do this every day
we we had a blast doing this
and I would do it more than once a year if I could
um very regularly we had a great time
so 3 2 1
oh
that's great
I'm so happy to see her smile so big
and I'm I know she's enjoying every minute of this as well
I always think she looks like a princess
and I was so happy to see the smile in her face
and looking so beautiful
so you could tell she was very happy
and that brought me happiness
let me hug you again you're wonderful
thank you grandma
예쁘다 엄마 좋을까 엄마 너무 예뻐 너무 예쁘다
that was so awesome wasn't that wonderful 감사합니다
oh oh hi hi
oh oh hi
I just see you I just see you
1,000 yeah thank you
so nice to meet you yeah thank you
so much my life is just cooking it's kitchen
I've never been like take care of myself it's all about work
나도 울 거 같아 I almost cry don't make me cry now no no way no way
no tears no tears
hi oh hi hi good to see you good to see you
hi hello nice to meet you chef came in
oh Emma it's hello again oh wow so amazing wow
wow did you did you have a good time I did I did
oh my God oh my God I love it I love it wow it
keeps on existing there oh my God oh my God
it keeps on existing there wow
hi how are you
I'm great I just wanted to come and say thank you and really
some sweets and and food from the restaurant and wow
you wanna you wanna have a seat oh my God we are so great
yeah we have time yeah
oh my God
can I open it yes
oh this is
this is what you're eating
what are you eating this is what you're eating
this is my favorite in New York
you know yeah
oh cake is there
oh my God what is that
and this is called the princess cake
is that rice cake mochi
uh no
like a mochi no
it could look like it but it's marzipan
so cute
what is that uh
it's very traditional it's like fish
ah you go
you go make the bread yes
it's tomato butter tomato butter
tomato butter
so you get to try a little bit of Swedish
Swedish food Swedish food
how do you think this idea
I sent the email
yeah I just felt like it wasn't enough
and then I figured let's bring the restaurant to you
oh my God
it's just too much thank you so much
well thank you
I'm gonna go to work yeah
I'll cook thank you thank you so much
good to see you good to see you
bye guys
bye bye
bye bye bye
have a nice day see you soon
see you soon bye bye love you
ㅎㅎ 음 음식을 해 갖고
왔어 그니까 정말 한국인의 정이야
마지막 날이라고 이렇게 음식을 해서 와줘 가지고 그것도 너무 감동이었고
어 그리고
너무 달라진 거예요 사람이 어 예뻐지기 위해서 노력하고 근데 자신을
아끼는 마음이 좀 많아진 거 같아서 그게 너무
좋았어요
엠마님이 약간 스웨덴 음식을 싸가지고 오셨는데 꼭 맛보세요 여러분
아셨죠 헤 궁금하다 뭐야 하는데 어 먹어보자
아니 아니 뭐를 이렇게 많이 주셨을까 이거
토마토 버터야 어머 어머 너무 먹어보고
싶었어요 저 너무 궁금했거든요 어 조금
찍어 좀 짜잔 하니까 아 누나 어 이 머스타드 조림을
꼭 먹어봐 어 이게 진짜 맛있어 이거 미쳤나 봐 어 진짜
이게 뭐야 이거는 고등어 봉조밥 같은 느낌이야 어 근데 이게
아린데 맛있어 고등어 봉조각 봉조밥 같은 느낌
아 봉조밥 일단은 그거를 누나 그냥 먹지 말고 요거 빵이
이게 밥이라고 생각하고 요거랑 같이 먹어야 돼 이게 밥이야 예스
huh huh
it is my best one yeah yeah oh wow this is so good this is so good
hmm
ㅎㅎㅎ 너 죄송해 입김 조금 흠
아 맛있지 어 나 신고이네 응 나 신고 좋아해
진짜 맛있어 응 얘도 맛있어 신고 아이 러브 해 아 지금 먹어
보려고요 지금
이거 이거를 얘랑 같이
아 미슐랭 투 스타에 맞아요 이렇게 탕비실에서 먹어도 되는
건가 와 미슐랭 투 스타의 요리를 탕비실에서 직접 만들어 준다던데
탕비실에서 그치 야 음
아 언니가 자꾸 입김 발사해 옆에서 맛있게 먹는다 음 와우 음 음
음 음 너무 맛있어
와우
어마어마하네 음 음 너무
맛있어요 어메이징하다 맛있죠 어 눈에서 막 별이
별이 있는 빵에 빵에 올려 먹으면 맛있어요
와 와 약간 오늘에서 별이 빛난다만 약간 응
진짜 블랙 그 맛집 냄새야 와 나 처음 먹어 봐 이러면 그죠 먹어 봤어
이러면 아니요
하 언니리야 대단하다 괜히 미스 블랙이 아니구나 음 음
음 와 머리 자르지도 자르지도 음 와 나
이거 일상 가고 싶다 근데 너무 맛있다 응
너무 고맙다 이 아침에 이걸 해가지고 아 근데 진짜 감사하다
음 다 드신 드신
거예요 다 먹었죠 다 먹었어 다 먹었어 음
고마워요
마지막 손님 마지막 손님 마지막 손님 그치 여기 넣는다
제 또 올 때 됐네요
welcome hi Sarah and Leah
Sarah Lia I'm Sarah nice to meet you I'm Sarah nice to meet you Lia
nice to meet you Lia nice to meet you too nice to meet you I'm Miran
and I'm the manager Rachel Rachel nice to meet you both
welcome nice to meet you that's beautiful up here let's see thank you
so please have a seat oh would you mind
oh thanks yeah thank you this one's a little heavy thank you
get a workout in
so how are you good good how are you excited
oh so we have a wake up drinks oh
oh banana milk latte yeah that is great on
I think I will try that like I should try this since
it sounds the most
yeah I'll do that too oh really uh huh okay great choice
so are you guys ready for the consultation yes yes please come
follow me
so follow me this way a little tie
how are you feeling about you know makeover thing good yeah we're
excited to try some new stuff
so wow you're just really twin you know
oh
okay
okay um
before we start do you have any allergies or concerns about your skin
or
no allergies
um just I sometimes have dryness so dryness moisture is great uh huh
yeah and you also mentioned redness yes
I'm I do tend to have like redness around like
and for me I think moisture and like um oh
so you are Sarah you're Leah right
like can you tell the difference
I know we look extra similar now we're all covered up
but OK now I can see it OK
hahaha
OK so what's your plan for today
my husband is out of town
but Sarah's husband who we always
we've been college friends for forever
so we're all doing like a trio date okay
um so we're gonna go get dinner together
dinner together and some drinks
so we'll have like a fresh
you know yeah
yes look nice for our
our get together
and it's gonna be really fun that we have a two artists
makeup artist there yeah
and each one of us so I could do it yeah
I love that it's gonna be different thing
uh huh you can just try more dramatical yeah
yeah yeah
makeup also so sure
yeah it's a little bit of like a trick for your husband
trick for your husband you know hahaha
see if they can tell us apart yeah
I'm gonna tell ask them you know
so I think that would be better if you try more something
something new one could be more just like
trust her nothing trust her yeah
leave it to me yeah
one could be more just like fresh face and one
could be a little bit more dramatic yeah
I I yeah like still still like natural but a little bit more yes
I would do the I
maybe I would do the dramatic with like the slightly blunter hair
just to see how that
yeah they're gonna find us
you know every single chance my name is Leah Brisky
I am a professional opera singer and I'm 31 years old hahaha
my name is Sarah I'm 31 years old
I live here in New York and I used to be a teacher before that
Sarah's my best friend she's my go to girl for anything
and I think the most special relationship in my life
I'm four minutes older than Leah
so I think I'm a little bit more but we both love to have a good time
we're both extroverted after this evening
going out to dinner with Leah and Andrew
okay great
so let's get started great
great so follow me this way please
진짜 나오셨다 아하 샴푸는 한 분만 하시면 됩니다 네 셀라만
셀라만 하시면 됩니다 아 네에요 하이
나이스 미트 유 한 분은 바로 폰이나 바로 폰이 가면 돼요 아 폰이름으로
is in blanket
so you're um what's your name Sarah Sarah yeah Sarah hi Sarah hi
I will recline your chair okay so just relax okay thank you
how's it feel good can you come up a bit just no mom gown
gown it was here that go ah
more handsome shall we put on gown how's the temperature
you could even go a little warmer if you'd like oh okay
alright
how's the water temperature
it was fine fine
어 처음에는 계속 불안하니까 말도
많이 했던 거 같은데 점점 고객님에 대한 편안함을 주고 싶다라는
생각이 계속 드는 거예요
this is good ah you don't have to hold it alright you can
is that alright uh huh just let me know if you feel uncomfy okay
okay sounds good thanks yeah
Sarah
I give you a little head massage okay so just let me know if it hurts
okay alright
was it alright that's nice thank you hahaha
I did my best hahaha thank you thanks
who is um who is older you or I'm four minutes older four minutes
oh my God
I want to be a swing it's fun yeah
you guys close each other
yeah we're super close best friends best friends
and you guys share your clothes
yeah not as much as when we were like in college but alright
when we're in town she's she doesn't have to pack any clothes
when she comes to visit
she's like I'll just get something from your closet so
what about what about your personality
I'm a little bit more organized
she's a little bit more like go with the flow alright
hi are you I'm Leah yeah yeah
nice to meet you nice to meet you too yeah I'm a pony
yeah p o n y that's so fun yeah it sounds yeah
my little pony right
yeah I think normal or dry skin
so I'm gonna use two products of for cream
so I use two blue creams
but your skin texture is so
so pretty
thank you
I'm gonna snap a picture of these two so I remember oh okay
thank you you're welcome
and so you would put all of these on before doing
make your makeup in the morning
of course really help with moisture
mm hmm yeah
I think you were best student in your high school hahaha
because you're studious yes
yes
uh
I heard about your dress color for today
mm hmm yeah
is this brown right
yeah it's like a dark brown
like chocolate brown oh
can I see it yeah
I had it earlier this week at an event this oh
the deep brown 1 mm hmm
uh it's gonna be uh
same with the makeup so I decision it would be good uh
totally different the makeup style
yeah so hmm
I'm gonna change a little bit the yeah
makeup to start with the outfit
mm hmm so I could do a little bit more like slightly smoky or yeah
yeah mm hmm good that's good
photo uh
on the pad I have one
so I have a lot of you go move the girl who do that thing competition
you think I need
근데 우리 막 다르게 할 걸로 눈이 해야 돼 그렇게 없이
그냥 하고 싶으면 하면 돼 어 나는 드레스 컬러에 맞추기로 해가지고
드레스 어떻게 했는데요 드레스가 딥 브라운이에요 둘이 근데 비슷한 옷
입는다 아니야 잘라 우리 딥 네이비에 화이트라고 했거든 아
그래서 나는 조금 무드 무드 있게 가려고 음 하나 뭐 하지 메이비라고
이게
사실은 어 레오랑 저랑 그냥 다르게 가보자 약간 이렇게 너프하기
얘기한 게 전부거든요 그러니까
서로 어떻게 할지 모르고 중간에 확인하면서 확인한 게
전문 거예요 음 아 벌써 재밌다 벌써 맛있다 음
so let's try I love that uh huh
and then we are gonna use the foundation okay
the colour test
I think it's good match
이제 저 같은
경우에는 드레스 무드에 맞췄어요 색깔이랑 무드에 조금
더 약간 태난 피부를 좀 살려서 했거든요
look up please I'm using correct colour
so you said you use the green corrector uh I use 2 colors hmm
OK using this salmon color uh huh yeah I use this color uh on the
like under eye yeah like eye bag area and then second is mint
I use the lower uh waterline okay and then uh
all of the yeah upper eyelid okay upper eye
learning learning from you yes yes just ask me that's good
remembering that one good student
and then I'm gonna use the brown color with your yeah match you
with your outfit so
this
OK
look down thank you can you look straight ahead hmm
and then we can use this colour for the outline hmm like this
okay close your eyes
oh you wanna see the yeah process yeah so that's why you like
every time like this and this
yeah OK
cause you you're
you're like reading me mm hmm right
hahaha you're onto me
mm hmm and then um yeah
난 정했어
yeah I heard you have a navy dress right now
uh for the after yeah
yeah I have a
a navy vest yeah
I think it'll be oh
oh my goodness hahaha
this orange brown will be really nice on you
I like that yeah let's do it
do you have any concern on your skin
I would say uh
redness is like my main concern
and then staying hydrated and lifted
as I'm getting a little bit older
uh huh
but you look still really good
thank you yeah
I envy you guys because I'm the only child
oh yeah
I wish I have another one with like a same like me right
yeah no
it's very fun being a twin wow
even as adults it's fun really
mm hmm wow
I think you're have a uh face heat
so it helps face heat gone
yeah you can use this as facial mask as well
can I take a picture of this
yeah of course
I'm gonna snap a picture of these two so I remember
oh okay
it's individual mask bag thanks
yeah major mask bag
음흠 이분은
헤어 뭐 하시나요 웨이브요 웨이브 그냥 풀린 에이브 자연스러워요
좀 더 볼륨 있고 좀 걸감이 있는 게 어울리는 얼굴이라 이제 밑으로
흘러가는데 이렇게 약간 로맨틱한 웨이브로 머리 해 드렸어
I'm in the holding me holding spray
you are the last client that's what he said yeah yeah
it's closing my salon
yeah time is very bright yeah time's so fast
and I will use this green corrector okay
so before makeup like this redness gone
uh huh
it's not dry at all so good hmm
oh yeah
that's nice yes
do you mind if I write this one down too
of course take a picture shy
shy shy
oh yeah
the redness is like much better yes
do you know the Cushion Foundation
cushion foundation you said yeah
this one because it has a cushion in it
like this oh
oh yeah
so and put this one here
like here that's nice
the redness is gone yeah
it's light it's not like thick yeah
no thick we Korean never use thick texture well
that's really nice cause I have fair skin
so like I love like Korean beauty and makeup
cause I feel like it's very good for like fair skin right
아
look at this that's really nice
와 봐봐요 얼굴 피부 봐요
너무 이뻐 스킨 진짜 피부 너무 좋으신데
so nice do you think you were uh warm uh autumn autumn warm tone
uh yes I am a warm I I got my colors done and I was a warm really
a warm oh well
light autumn soft autumn soft autumn oh oh
how is it supposed to rubles she's an expert so what do you think hmm
check this and
I checked your colour sure
this is warm this is cool
you could check really cool cool
yes wow
yes it's right
we are checking this this line and the this
oh my God yeah
York is very cool too cool yeah
this is an we'll check to do here
it's cool right
summer right and then it's warm right
yes more than good is in summer right
hmm
let's check to do this it's good hmm OK
exactly this the your colour is summer white OK light
yeah summer
summer white is in good choice colour is pastel hmm
do you like pastel colour
I do I like lavender yes
lavender pink pastel pink
pastel blue exactly
it's a good item OK
colour do you like I do yeah
it's exactly your colour is some alright OK
some alright to say 선물 아이템에 나 이것 써서
어떡해 네 선물 아이템에 나 지금 이런 걸로 써서 어떡해 괜찮아요
그건 이건 그냥 갖고 계신 거고요 응
there's a
uh I think we gonna change the eye shadow colors okay
with this one and with this one okay let's mix okay it's okay mm hmm
어 이 메 이 메이크업을 이 데님이라 매치 시켰을 때 너무 더워 보일
것 같은 거예요 저는 살아의
에너지가 굉장히 차분한 느낌이었어 가지고 퍽퍽하고 좀 더 라이트한
그런 느낌이 입었을 때 훨씬
잘 살릴 수 있는 느낌이 있는 거 같아서 어 되게 핑크
바이올렛으로 좀 바꿔야지 해서 이제 바이올렛 쪽으로 바꾼 거예요
oh
come on come on
wow I love this color
it looks really nice yes
don't you let anybody
ever break your stride
keep moving
so just remember like
it looks good Obrigado
oh my God Obrigado
내가 집에 있을 때 내 옷도 안 들여 있는데 참
내 옷을 열심히 다려 봐야겠다
다리니까 좋네요
oh hello how are you oh hello how are you good how are you
so you're Sarah's
husband right I am oh damn nice to meet you nice to meet you uh huh
so please have a seat here thank you
just right here is better yeah
my place yes so we have our welcome drinks and snacks
oh wow
I love uh awesome tea what about snack too I'm OK
you're OK with that yeah OK thank you you're welcome
it's a little bit of like a trick for your husband you know hahaha
see if they can tell the part yeah
no snack no I'm okay okay yes thank you they are twins
same yeah hahaha same yeah
Sarah Lia oh who's who's Sarah
yes they look very similar yeah very similar
how are you you know who's
Sarah just over time I guess I just Learned okay
are you player trombone
I am oh Leah's husband too yes Colin yeah
so nice yeah the musician family mm hmm mm hmm
yeah
Sarah Leah
Saraelia Saraelia Saraelia
이분 노래한다고 했던 거 같은데 헬리어 유싱 I do yeah wow
오페라 오페라 오페라 yeah
can I hear that
can you hear a little bit please
what's that oh
my God what's that
oh my God
not so bad not too bad
o Sol é MEU
what we got a whole house
it's like very like forward
yeah it's like yeah
maybe too forward hahaha
good good
hahaha what
oh that was so funny
I want to I want to sing
hear your song oh gosh
I don't even know um
아우 ㅎㅎ 너무 잘생겼다 아빠 아 떼라 하셨다 그랬지
아 아 음악이 없어 노 뮤직 음악이 노 뮤직 ㅎㅎ 미용실에 소리가
없으니까 너무 정적이 갑자기 너무 정적해져 ㅎㅎ
wow oh good song bravo
bravo
oh my goodness oh my God
have you guys follow me around wow oh my God
wow this room filled yeah with your voice
you guys need to be my audience just like all the time wow there's
another music star really yeah hahaha did you run out
너무 오셨습니다 is it hurt no
두
분이 머리 엄청 쏙 빠다
어 뭐 두 사람 앉은 다른 사람들도 나올 거 같아요 어 응
사실 좀 남편도 오고 그래서 쌍둥이지만 서로
이렇게 다른 느낌도 만들 수 있다는 걸 보여주고 싶은
거였거든 저는 그리고 또
의상을 보고 나서 이제 약간 프렌치 시크
같은 느낌으로 그냥 소프트한 업
그 한국에서 그냥 데일리하게 하는 업으로 이렇게 해줬어요
예 좋아요
이 싱이라고 싱 머리 헤드 헤드가 너무
적어서 어떻게 쓰는 거지 응 처음 봤는데
그걸 머리 속에 넣어요 넣을 거예요 수시 없어서 아 그렇게 나이스
아 가짜 머리 오 마이 갓 오 마이
갓 오 마이 갓
you look amazing thank you I love your hair
and I'm excited to see how Sarah's is different yes yeah
hmm and to see what Andrew what Andrew says oh
Ja it's alright yes OK now it's time let's go out yes
now finally
who is she I
I I don't remember that
oh um
I I can't you
it's really hard to find the difference between
you know who is that
Sarah maybe Sarah
Sarah first I don't know
I have no idea we don't know
yeah ha ha ha
whoever comes first yes
whoever comes first I don't know that
oh now I'm done
yeah oh
oh my God
wow what do we think
so beautiful
yeah
wow
I like it thanks
what do you think about the makeup
nice and fresh right
a little drama little drama hair hahaha
yeah yeah
this is mine this is mine yeah
yeah nice
I know I'm excited
wow we were like
will you be able to tell us apart
who am I who am I
who am I nearly OK
hahaha
just checking just checking hahaha
well I'm going out of me
it will look good for going out
going out afterwards yeah
I need it dress up a little bit more hahaha
oh Sarah Nauna yeah
oh she's coming
yeah cover your eyes hahaha
open it wow
oh my God
just one two three
one two
three go
let's go ah
oh my God
wow
oh wow
oh my gosh your hair looks great
that's so sweet
I said like the the way
oh my God
look at you do we look like
do we look like twins now
yeah you still know that this one's Sarah
피부 깨끗하다 그래야
되나 진짜 말이 갔어요 그래서 피부 톤도 되게 깨끗하고 하얘게 연출을
해드렸거든요 아 레오는
뭔가 조금 더 케이비티에 이런 약간 브이밍한 그런 느낌에 초점을 뒀구나
그런데 이제
저 같은 경우에는 조금 더 약간 태닝 피부를 좀 살려서 했거든요
저는 무조건 아웃핏 봐요 먼저 보고 그 톤에 맞게 하자
근데 대님 이었더라고요 그래서 어 되게
핑크 마이올레스로 좀 더 화사한 느낌 연출해 드리고 싶었어요
드레스 무드에 맞췄어요 색깔이랑
무드에 그래서 전반적으로 저는 되게 웜하게 나왔고
좀 분위기 있게 연출을 해서
이게 화사함과 좀 그간 그거의 차이가 좀 있었던 거 같아요
쌍둥이지만 서로 이렇게 다른 느낌도 만들 수 있다는 걸 보여주고 싶은
걸거든 저는
so beautiful
so pretty oh my God
you're like 90s though I know wow look at the eyelashes
I said I was ready to do a concert now
yeah I know I said blackpink like watch out haha
watch out I'm like with the with the eye makeup I'm like K Beauty
oh no one saw that oh
yeah it's been so fun now you get to see how glamorous we can be oh
thank you guys so much this is so nice thank you guys
thank you to Rachel
perfect ending ending customer thank you for coming
thank you so much
자 모입시다 아
마지막이에요 자 모입시다 여러분들 너무너무
고생하셨습니다 너무 감사드립니다 모두 다
이번에는 어떻게 살살 할까요 크게 할까요 크게 해야죠 크게 해야죠 자
그러면 배 속에 힘을 다 모아서 허허
찍었어요 아 찍었어요
레오야 아 너무 슬퍼했어 아 아 누구 밟았어 누구 밟았어
아 저 영한이 없습니다
너무 하 언없이 머리 많이 해 봤어요 후회가 없어요 네
제가 이제 마흔 다섯 살인데 그 어렸을 때 너무 밥 굶으면서
굶주워 가지고 고객님들 만나고 머리
해줄 때가 떠올라서 너무 행복했어요 근데
문을 닫네 따라 하지 마세요
근데 다 너무 고마웠는데 특히 종혁 씨한테 감사하죠 많이 도와줬죠 ㅎㅎ
일머리가 있었던 거 같습니다 ㅎㅎ 막상
이렇게 끝나니까
그래도 아쉬움이 좀 남는 시원섭섭한
기분이에요 잘하네 아무것도 모르는
제가 옆에서 어시스트를 한다라는 거는
정말 영광스러운 일이잖아요
너무
감사하고 마음가짐도 달라져요 선생님들에 대한 어떤
리스펙트 이 굉장히
높아졌습니다 진짜 대단하신 분들이고요 어 좋아하고 만족을 할 법도 한데
이분들은 시간 얘기를 안 해주면 끝도 없이 할 수 있을 것 같은 느낌
진짜 어떻게든 시간이 문제가 아니라 내가 한국 대표로
손을 대신해서 왔으니까
어떻게든 예쁘게 해서 보내야겠다가 목표였거든요
처음에 그래서 대체 케이를 매번 했던 것 같아 아침 저녁으로 그때
뭔가
딱 단합되는 느낌이었어요 아 우리 하나의 팀이야 이러면서 꽃단장 저는
아무래도 팀으로 이렇게 일해 본 적이 거의 처음이거든요
그러다 보니까 되게 함께 만든 작업물 같았고 너무 좋았어요
너무 완벽한 팀이었어
모든 직원들이 정말 한 마음이 돼야
이게 팀워크로 이루어질 수 있다는 걸 알게
돼서 이제 샵에 가면 좀 다른 느낌으로 볼 거
같아요 저는 항상 샵에 손님으로 가는 입장인데
이제 반대로 돼 보니까 자 옵니다 마음이 스카미
스카미 그 마음이 느껴지잖아요 근데 되게 어 뭔가
감동적인 게 있다 이건 확실히 문클한 지점이 있다 이런 생각이 들었어요
여러분들 너무 아름다웠어요 고마웠어요 와줘서 아
아
앉아 진짜 늙어서 그런지 머리가 많아졌어 아하하하 아 이거 아까 우리
점심 먹을 아 내 포켓인데 정말 러비어스 님 파하십시오 어
oh no I'm sorry
would you mind if they put a little bit of like a cake beauty
that's so weird that's so weird it's OK it's OK it's OK
are you a hairstylist too baby listen
I ain't gonna take your proposition
welcome I'll tell you baby before you better listen
don't go tripping on me
아이고 정들어서 어떡해요 자 마지막 볼 꿉니다 네 아이고 올렸다
아하하하
안녕 마이 마이 하나 둘 허밍스 예 마이 안녕 어두워졌어도 안녕 갑시다
안녕 아 당장
안녕 너무 싫어 하나 둘 셋
loved you from the start
I love you from the stars
안녕